<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Profiles on rs-team</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/</link><description>Recent content in Profiles on rs-team</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>abaddon</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/abaddon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/abaddon/</guid><description>Nikos Oikonomou (abaddon) I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Dev turned PenTester and The Creator of this fine web portal.
About me I always considered coding easy and fun, I later found out that breaking stuff was way more exciting. That should be reason enough for anyone with a CS background to get into PenTesting. That, and the fact that you get to be called a &amp;ldquo;hacker&amp;rdquo;.
Fields of expertise Linux (I use Arch btw) PenTesting Binary Exploitation Scripting (need a quicker way to do something?</description></item><item><title>mikts</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/mikts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/mikts/</guid><description>Mike Tsoukatos (mikts) I&amp;rsquo;m a DevOps Engineer based in Athens, Greece.
About me I love studying new technologies and tools and automating infastructure deployments. My other passion is penetration testing and ctf challenges. Also I always try to take advantage of DevOps best practices to incorporate security testing in the development pipelines.
Automate everything!
Fields of expertise Linux Scripting Automation Docker Interests Petting Cats Breaking things Wannabe Chef State of mind Life is a party and im the pinata!</description></item><item><title>november</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/november/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/profiles/november/</guid><description>Nikos Mantas (november) I&amp;rsquo;m a Cyber Incident Responder for the Big(4) Green Dot in Athens, Greece.
About me I never liked exploits and injections. But my friends did. So they became hackers. Now I have no friends&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;ve ended up performing necromancy on dead computers (the official term, you might have heard of is post-mortem forensics) and hunting cyber witches (i.e threat hunting). I seek redemption by catching the bad guys.</description></item></channel></rss>