<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on res3rveShells</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on res3rveShells</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PoSh Cheatsheet</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/posh-cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/posh-cheatsheet/</guid><description>PowerShell Cheatsheet for Incident Response During September we competed in PoSh-Hunter, a jeopardy style CTF to test our PowerShell skills in triage (and host enumeration). The flags were mostly the output of a command relating to one of the following 8 challenges: - Encryption\Cipher - Filesystem - Registry - Logs\ Tasks - Enterprise Services - DNS - Data Manipulation - Q\A
Rules of engagement Download the PoSh Hunter VM and log in using the credentials provided Use the PoSh Hunter VM to answer the challenges (minus the Q/A general PowerShell knowledge questions) The point value for questions varies based on difficulty</description></item><item><title>LaCasaDePapel Hack The Box Writeup</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/lacasadepapel-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 11:04:51 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/lacasadepapel-writeup/</guid><description>Machine Info LaCasaDePapel is an Easy difficulty machine in the Hack The Box platform that that tests your certificate knowledge and some basic CVE knowledge for the user part of the box. The root part of the box is easier than the user requiring basic enumeration and linux os knowledge.
Solution Enumeration Classic nmap enumeration
sudo nmap -Pn -sV -sT -T4 -oN ports.txt lacasadepapel.htb Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate the open ports 21,80,443:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/about/</guid><description>Mission Members Nikos Mantas (november) I&amp;rsquo;m a Cyber Incident Responder for the Big(4) Green Dot in Athens, Greece.
About me: I never liked exploits and injections. But my friends did. So they became hackers. Now I have no friends&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;ve ended up performing necromancy on dead computers (the official term, you&amp;rsquo;ve might have heard of is post-mortem forensics) and hunting cyber witches (i.e threat hunting). I seek redemption by catching the bad guys.</description></item><item><title>Content</title><link>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/content/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://res3rveshells.github.io/posts/content/</guid><description> Useful Resources and cheatsheets</description></item></channel></rss>